JAMEEL AHMED

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

SUMARY

I am a highly skilled react developer with extensive experience, I have completed more than 50 web projects individually. I pride myself on my problem-solving mindset and my attention to detail. My career goals include continuing to grow as a front-end expert while exploring new areas in web development.

CONTACT

Phone: +92 310 8495112

Email: Jameelahmedkalhoro@gmail.com

Address: Sukkur City, Sindh, Pakistan

SKILLS

- Node
- React.js
- JavaScript
- Next.js
- TypeScript
- Nest.js
- Python
- GitHub
- Express.js
- Three.is
- PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Sukkur IBA University

LANGUAGES

- English Proficient
- Urdu Native

PROJECTS

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jameelahmed-33v/
- Github: https://github.com/Jameel-Kalhoro

EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer

AutoMyChat • August 2023 - January 2024 Sukkur, Pakistan

- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to identify and prioritize features and requirements
- Conduct code reviews and provide feedback to improve code quality
- Develop and execute unit tests and perform system testing to ensure software quality
- Creating Components for Front-end and Back-end

Full-Stack Developer

Trustversy • June 2024 - September 2024 Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

- Developed and maintained multiple Reactbased web applications.
- Integrated applications with RESTful APIs using Axios and other related libraries.

Web Front-End Developer

Fiverr • August 2019 - Current

- · Collaborated with other developers using Git and Github for version control.
- Contributed to the development of a largescale React-based web application.
- Utilized Agile methodologies for project management and development.
- Integrated React with Three.js Participated in code reviews and provided feedback to other team members